[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "cap_tal",
    "options": ["I", "E", "A"],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "tow_ring",
    "options": ["E", "A", "O"],
    "answer": "E"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "riv_ers",
    "options": ["V", "E", "R"],
    "answer": "V"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "telepho_e",
    "options": ["L", "N", "R"],
    "answer": "N"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "paint_ng",
    "options": ["I", "E", "A"],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "squa_re",
    "options": ["R", "T", "U"],
    "answer": "R"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "buil_ing",
    "options": ["D", "T", "S"],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "ele_ents",
    "options": ["M", "L", "T"],
    "answer": "M"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "plane_t",
    "options": ["A", "E", "I"],
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "mo_nlit",
    "options": ["O", "O", "A"],
    "answer": "O"
  }
]